Guide to the Labor Research Association Records TAM 129
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Subseries II:B: Officers Correspondence, Robert Dunn
    - Student Requests, 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Towsen, Gus, 1962-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Trachtenberg, Alexander, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - United Electrical Workers-Canada, 1960-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Wellman, Saul, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 10a.)
    - Wheeler, George, 1954-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Walter, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Workers Health Bureau, 1924-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - World Marxist Review, 1959-1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Dunn Correspondence-A, 1928-1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence-B, 1925-1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence-C, 1941-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - General Correspondence-D, 1918-1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - General Correspondence-E, 1951-1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - General Correspondence-F, 1930-1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - General Correspondence-G, 1944-1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - General Correspondence-H, 1918-1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - General Correspondence-I, J, 1953-1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - General Correspondence-K, 1957-1966 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - General Correspondence-L, 1917-1966 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - General Correspondence-M, 1941-1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - General Correspondence-N, 1924-1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - General Correspondence-O, 1944-1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - General Correspondence -P, 1925-1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - General Correspondence-Q, R, 1935-1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - General Correspondence-S, 1948-1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - General Correspondence-T, 1951-1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - General Correspondence-U, V, 1927-1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence-W, 1941-1975 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - General Correspondence-X, Y, Z, 1937-1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - General CorrespondenceUnknown, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Subseries II:C: Other Officers Correspondence
    - Bailly, Gerald, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Harris, Joseph, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Harris, Lement, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Hutchins, Grace, 1931-1966 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Hutchins, Grace - Personal, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Rochester, Anna, 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Series III: Reports and Research Notes
  (1925-1974) 1.56 linear feet
  - Accounting Terminology, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - American Aid to USSR, 1957-1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - American Trade Unions and USSR, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Communism, 1936-1939 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Labor Organizations, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Automation, 1952-1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bibliographies-Labor Research, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Biographical Sketches-Prominent Right-Wingers A-I, 1930-1947 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Biographical Sketches-Prominent Right-Wingers J-Z, 1932-1960 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Black Americans, 1937-1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CIA/FBI, 1953-1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Civil Liberties, 1936-1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Constitutional Education League, 1931-1937 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dates to Remember, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Disarmament, 1956-1962 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Discrimination, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - East Asia, 1950-1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Economic Planning, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Elections, 1947-1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Farm Labor, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Finnish Federation, 1933-1939 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1935-1938 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Trade, 1930-1956 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Furniture Worker, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Health, 1932-1963 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Housing, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - PLACEKEEPING FOLDER -- 27 - 27D TO SERIES V. PUBLICATIONS, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Industrial and Economic Notes-Ward, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Industry, 1931-1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Informers, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - International Business and Industry, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Japan, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Labor History, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Labor History Dates, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Labor Unions, 1934-1959 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - LaFollette Hearings-Indexes, 1936-1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Latin America, 1928-1966 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Memos, 1931-1950 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Monopolies, 1931-1974 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Monopoly and Science, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - National Recovery Act, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - New England LRA, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - New Jersey, 1925-1932 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - N.Y.C.--Economic Crisis-Joe Harris, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - New York State, 1930-1933 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Ohio LRA, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Outlines, 1929-1937 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Pen and Hammer, 1930-1934 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Polish Almanac, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Press, 1933-1971 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Railroads, 1934-1958 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Rank and File Federation, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Reader's Scope, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Releases and Special Reports, 1928-1951 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Reports for Unions, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Reports, notes, miscellaneous, 1932-1966 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Research in Economic Trends-Victor Perlo, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Scientific Research, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Seizure of Daily Worker, 1955-1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Southern Industry, 1941-1957 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Standard Oil, 1931-1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Strikes, Importance of Statistics, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Taxation, 1932-1934 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Trade Union Unity League--Memos, 1929-1933 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Unemployed Councils, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Unemployment, 1929-1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Unemployment Release, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - USSR, 1931-1938 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - US Economy, 1932-1959 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Wages, 1935-1962 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - War Profits, 1932-1961 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Women, 1925-1959 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Manuscripts
  (1920-1976) 1.65 linear feet
  - Alaska-Samuel Weinman, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - American Farmer-Moe Bragin, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - American Begro-Samuel Weinman, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Banking, History in the US, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Capitalist Press in the Class War, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Changing Structure of the Working Class (Preface)-J.M. Buddish, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Chain Stores, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - China Unites-Janet McDonald, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Civil Liberties Study-LRA, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Coal and Nationalization-Ted Allen, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Deportations, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Economic Basis of the Political Situation-LRA, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Economic Reform-Victor Perlo, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Espionage I (Labor Spy) - Howard and Dunn, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Espionage IIIa " ", 1920 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Espionage IIIb " ", 1920 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Espionage IV General Correspondence, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Film Industry, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Germans in US Unions-Karl Oberman, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Great Fortunes, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Group Insurance--Appendix-Horace B. Davis, ca.1933 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - High Cost of Living Material, ca.1936 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Housing-Lilian Zahn, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Imperialism and Labor-Horace Davis, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Isolationist Trends-Ted Allen, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Ku Klux Klan-Gil Stark, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Labor and Construction Bibliography, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Labor Fact Book II, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Labor and Social Conditions, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Labor in the South Chp.3-5; Ester Lowell, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Labor in the South-Notes, Comments, 1933-1935 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Lawrence, MA, ca.1932 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Liberia-Samuel Weinman, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Metalworking Industry-Victor Perlo, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mexico-Robert Winter, ca.1935 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Negro Question, Revolutionary Traditions, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Negroes, New Jersey-Harold Weaver, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - New York Call, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Oil, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Our USA-Fleisher, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Peace Issues, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Postal Substitutes-Max Rothman, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Production Questionaires, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Quote Book, 1939-1942 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Radio-Zacharoff, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Schools in the USSR, 1932-1933 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Shoes--Appendix-Horace Davis, ca.1940 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Southern Differential-Herbert Aptheker, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Southern Lumbering-Art Shields/Ester Lowell, 1929, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Steel-Ted Allen, ca.1948 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Surplus Value, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Telephone Companies, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Textiles--Dual Unions-Dunn, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Tobacco-J. Troxell, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - USSR Pamphlet, 1933-1936 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Violence Study, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Visual Education Press, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Wages-Jacob Oser, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - War to End Wars, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Workers Education Pamphlet, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Workers in Industrial America-Godell, 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Work Loads, Speed-up, and Take Home Pay, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Series V: Publications
  (1929-1974) .35 linear foot
  - Arsenal Of Facts, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - LRA Booklets, 1929-1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - British Workers in the War, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Clothing Workers, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Daily Worker/World-LRA Arcticles, 1930-1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Federated Press-LRA Articles, 1929-1931 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Federated Press-LRA Articles, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Forced Labor in the US, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - History of the Shorter Workday, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Index for Economic Notes, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 9a.)
  - Index for Mining Notes, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 9b)
  - Index for NRA Notes, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 9c)
  - Index For Steel and Metal Notes, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Index For Textile Notes, 1932-1939 (Box 6, Folder 9e)
  - International Pamphlets, 1930-1948 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Labor Fact Book 1-Reviews, etc., 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Labor Fact Book 2-Reviews, etc., 1934 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Labor Fact Book 3-Reviews, etc., 1936 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Labor Fact Book 4-Reviews, etc., 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Labor Fact Book 5-Reviews, etc., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Labor Fact Book 6-Reviews, etc., 1943-1947 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Labor Fact Book 7-Reviews, etc., 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Labor Fact Book 8-Reviews, etc., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Labor Fact Book 9-Reviews, etc., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Labor Fact Book 10, 11-Reviews, etc. 1953-55, 1953-1955 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Labor Fact Book 12, 13-Reviews, etc. 1955-56, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Labor Fact Book 14-17-Reviews, etc., 1958-1965 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Labor and Industry Series, 1931-1935 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - LRA Articles, 1930-1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Labor and Steel--Reviews, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Labor Unity--LRA Articles, 1929-1935 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Monopoly in the U.S., 1942 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Questionaires, 1931-1935 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Marine Workers Voice--LRA Articles, 1933-1935 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - New Masses--LRA Articles, 1938-1947 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Railroads in Crisis, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Shoe and Leather Notes, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Trade Union Facts, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Trends in American Capitalism, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Series VI: Dunn-Political Activities, Writings, Memorabilia
  (1914-1973) .63 linear foot
  - Dunn--Activities, 1936-1953 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Dunn--Articles, 1914-1937 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Dunn--Articles, 1938-1969 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Bail Fund--Civil Rights Congress, 1948-1973 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - HUAC Hearings, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Dunn--Personal Correspondence, 1922-1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Dunn--Personal and Family Memorabilia, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Soviet Famine Relief, 1921-1966 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Soviet Trade Union Delegation, 1927-1928 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - USSR--Notes, Memorandum, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - USSR--Factory Visits, Interviews, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - USSR--Trade Union Agreements, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Workers School Lectures, 1927-1937 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Dunn--Yale Memorabilia, 1954-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Dunn--Scrapbook, 1915-1923 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Series VII: Labor Spies
  - American Confidential Bureau (New York City, N.Y.), 1936 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Baldwin Felts Agency (Colorado, West Va., elsewhere), 1921-1932 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bell Detective Agency (New Jersey, Philadelphia), 1930 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bergoff Detective Service (New York City, N.Y., elsewhere), 1929-1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Bibliographies, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Blossom, Frederick: socialist accused of fraud, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Burke Detective Agency, Robert Burke: Interview and article.., 1920-1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Burns Detective Agency (California, New York, elsewhere), 1911-1939 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Communist Party U.S.A. (spies against), 1925-1950 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Company Spies and Spy Systems, 1925-1935 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Corporations Auxiliary Co; a.k.a. "International Auxiliary Co.: (Illinois, N.Y., Ohio, Tn., Wisconsin, elsewhere), 1920-1937 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Corporations Auxiliary Co: Report on exposure of Spies in Hartford Ct., 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Crimes by Labor Spies, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dunn, Robert: Writings by L.R.A. co-founder, 1926-1929 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Eagle Detective Agency, renamed Sherwood Detective Agency (New York City), 1920-1937 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Fosters Industrial & Detective Bureau (New Jersey, New York), 1925 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Government Hired Labor Spies: Federal and Local Governments, 1930-1950 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Howard W. Russel Inc. (Milwaukee, Wis.)., 1924-1926 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Labor Spies Agencies: miscellaneous material, 1921-1948 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Labor Spies: individuals, 1925-1945 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Labor Spies: general material, 1919-1950 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Laws Against Labor Spies, 1925-1937 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Lessig, Adolph: Alleged Labor Spy (New Jersey, New York, elsewhere), 1921-1926 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Lessig, Adolph, 1927-1954 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Lessig, Adolph: Stenographic transcript of hearing, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Lessig, Adolph: Alleged Labor Spy, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - A.R. Macdonald Inc & Alfred R. Macdonald, 1924-1929 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Manning Detective Agency (Massachussets, New Jersy, New York), 1931-1934 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Newhouse, Edward (journalist), 1934 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - New Jersey Labor Spies: Passaic Strike & other, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - New Jersey Transportation: Strike of 1926, 1920-1926 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - New Jersey Union Leader Corruption (including Henry Hilfers), 1926-1932 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - New York City Government Spies Against Labor, 1932-1936 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Nosovitsky, Jacob (labor spy), 1920-1937 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Nosovitsky, Jacob :Report: "Framing Senator LaFollette in 1924", 1926 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Obrien, Jack (labor spy), 1927-1935 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - O'Neil Secret Service, 1932-1935 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Organisations of Private Detectives, 1928-1930 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - O'Toole Detective Agency, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Pinkerton Detective Agency :Reports & other, 1920-1954 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Pinkerton Detective Agency: United States Congress Report on Pinkertons., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Philadelphia Hosiery Plant: Reports by spy(s), 1926-1936 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Railway Audit & Inspection Co. (Labor Spy Co.) (Pennsylvania), 1914-1939 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Sherman Service Inc.: Interviews, correspondence, other (Massachussets, elsewhere), 1918-1926 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Sherman Service Inc.: Reports, interview, other (Massachussets, elsewhere), 1927-1934 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Spolansky, Jacob (Passaic, N.J., elsewhere), 1926-1933 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Steel Industry Spies: Reports, articles, other (Chicago, Pennsylvania, elsewhere), 1924-1936 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Steel Industry Spies: Reymer, William: Alleged Spy (Pennsylvania), 1935 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Steel Industry Spies: McMullin, H.R.: Alleged Spy (Michigan, Pennsylvania), 1934-1936 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Strike Breakers, 1922-1935 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Strikes: Transit & Labor in Philadelphia, 1926-1927 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - J.H. Turner Service Inc. (New York City, elsewhere)., 1911-1930 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - United Detective Bureau, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - U.S. Senate Hearings on Labor Spies, 1936-1939 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Violence by Labor Spies :interview, reports, other, 1920-1938 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Williams Service, George Williams (New York, Illinois), 1929-1934 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Wilmark Service System, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Series VIII: Unprocessed Materials from Earlier Accessions Relating to "Professional Patriots," "Labor Spies," and other Right-Wing Individuals and Organizations, undated (Box 10-14)
  - Unprocessed Materials from Earlier Accessions: 1, undated (Box 10)
  - Unprocessed Materials from Earlier Accessions: 2, undated (Box 11)
  - Unprocessed Materials from Earlier Accessions:3, undated (Box 12)
  - Unprocessed Materials from Earlier Accessions: 4, undated (Box 13)
  - Unprocessed Materials from Earlier Accessions: 5, undated (Box 14)
- Series IX: Addendum 2010, 1927-2001 (Box 15)
  - American Russian Institute: Services Available for Students and Teachers, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Clinton, Bill: Framed Letter Greeting LRA's 22nd Annual Award Dinner, Oct 29, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - De Maio, Ernest: Death and Memorial, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - De Maio, Ernest: Words for Workers [Glossary, 206 pp.], undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Economic Notes: Correspondence, Business, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Economic Notes: Index, Volume I (Dec 1932-Dec 1933), ca. 1934 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Economic Situation (typescript, 83 pp.), Nov 15, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Financial Aid Solicitation; History of Tax Status, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Hutchins, Grace: Affadavit of Cremation, Jul 19, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Hutchins, Grace: Corespondence, 1940-1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Hutchins, Grace: Memorial Service and Burial, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - "Labor against War...Statements...by Labor Groups...", ca. 1940 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Labor Law Reform Campaign, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1927-1950 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1975-1988 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Minutes (partial), 1991-2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund, Inc.: Reports on Conditions of Farm Workers, 1961-1965 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Notes, Brief: "Labor in World War II", 1940s (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Notes: "Labor in Last War and Today", ca. 1941 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Notes: Prices and Wages in Wartime, 1940s (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Perlo, Victor: Untitled Article Typescript [for the Worker] on the History of LRA, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Press Runs for LRA Periodicals: Incomplete, 1936-1973 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Questions and Answers: "Right to Work" [ILWU Research Department], cac. 1958 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Reconstruction/Post-War Planning Reports and Statements from Other Organizations [and LRA?], 1945-ca. 1950 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Trade Union Action: Subscription Promotion Memo, Aug 1, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Workers in the Crisis (Typescript, 15 pp.), ca. early 1930s (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - The Workers Health Bureau: A Brief History [19 pp., by Robert Dunn?], ca. 1928 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Year Book of American Labor, 1992-1993: Correspondence, Reports, etc., 1992-2000 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Series X: Addendum 2012
  - 22nd-25th Annual Labor Awards Dinners Planning Materials and Programs; LRA Pension Information and Documents Related to Tax Exempt Status; and Year-End Financial Statements, 1997-2008 (Box 16)
  - 26th-31st Annual Labor Awards Dinners Planning Materials and Programs and District 65 Pension Plan, et al. v. Labor Research Association, late 1970s-1980s, 1993-2008 (Box 17)
  - LRA Tax Status History; Year-End Financial Statements; By-Laws; Agreement with United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Workers of America (UAW), Local 2179; Board of Directors Minutes; and Five VHS Tapes of 2007 Annual Labor Awards Dinner, ca. 1982-2008 (Box 18)
  - Financial Statements and Tax Returns (dating from 1940s-1980s), 1944-2002 (Box 19)
  - Financial Statements, 1996-2004 (Box 20)
  - Two Cassette Tapes, Two Mini DVs, 23 CDs, and Four DVDs of Labor Awards Dinners and Various Events; Contact Sheets and Negatives from the 2000 Dinner; Slides from the 1998 and 1999 Dinners; and Photographs of Various Labor Leaders and Politicians (including Mark Green and Jesse Jackson), ca. 1993-2009 (Box 21)